紙牌屋
前情提要
翻譯   國士章魚X
翻譯   咖喱味的虛寒
翻譯   PiPi
翻譯   杏仁斯嘉麗
翻譯   吃冰棒
翻譯   WalkingNerd
翻譯   煮粥
時間軸   壬虛浪影
時間軸   噃噃
后期   餓得慌
顧問   老杜
校對   草草
總監   草草
紙牌屋
人人影視傾情奉獻
第五季  第六集
部分州不能認證結果
克萊爾·安德伍德  美國代總統
特許安全權限
弗蘭西斯·安德伍德
發信人: 舊友/新敵
我警告過你  叫走那些狗  否則還會繼續
警察內部備忘錄早已斷定商店爆炸系因燃氣泄漏后
聯調局才被召來  新證據顯示"襲擊"系捏造
安東尼·莫雷蒂  2次通話
安東尼·莫雷蒂
紀念基金
雅加達星報
道格·斯坦普  瑞秋·波斯納
-不是我的總統  -不是我的總統
- Not my president! - Not my president!
人民很憤怒
The people are angry.
國會吵成一團
The Congress is in disarray,
最高法院少了一位法官  必將陷入僵局
the Supreme Court is down a justice and doomed to deadlock,
而行政機關也群龍無首
and the executive branch is without a boss.
我必須告訴你  國會對同時為
I need to tell you, there is a lot of pushback on the Hill
總統和副總統投票抵觸情緒很高
about the simultaneous vote for president and VP.
你和他們想要的東西一樣
You want what they all want.
更好的地位
A better seat at the table.
這我可以給你
And that is something that I can give you.
艾丹
Aidan?
你應該趁還有機會逃出來
You should've gotten out when you had the chance.
你覺得你就逃出來了
You think you're out?
不只是他如何處理了那些數據
It's not just what he did with all the data.
艾丹之前能接觸到一切
Aidan had access to everything.
做你本該做的事
Do what you were supposed to do.
取消阻撓議事  好讓參議院能投票
Move the anti-filibuster measure forward so the Senate can vote.
-不行  -不行
- No. - No.
投票無結果
The vote is inconclusive.
你和康威都沒達到26票
Neither you nor Conway to 26.
我不管他們說什么
I don't care what they say,
我就是該死的美國總統
I'm fucking President of the United States.
不  你不是
No, you're not.
直到眾議院做出決定
The vice president will be acting president
副總統將代總統職
for as long as it takes the House to decide.
本人  克萊爾·黑爾·安德伍德
I, Claire Hale Underwood,
在此莊嚴宣誓
do solemnly swear
我必忠實執行
that I will faithfully execute the office
合眾國總統職務
of President of the United States...
我真為她驕傲  這是她應得的
I'm proud of her. She deserves this.
哪怕只能當幾個星期
Even if it only lasts for a couple of weeks.
忠于職守  竭盡全力
And will, to the best of my ability,
恪守  維護和捍衛
preserve, protect, and defend
合眾國憲法  愿上帝助我
the Constitution of the United States, so help me God.
恭喜你  代總統女士
Congratulations, Madam Acting President.
-感覺有什么不一樣嗎  -沒有
- Feel different? - No.
-騙我  -暫時而已  我只是代總統
- Liar. - It's temporary. I'm only acting.
現在你得全天候隨身帶著這個了
You have to now carry this with you at all times.
-密碼嗎  -沒錯  法律規定的
- The codes? - Mmm- hmm. It's the law.
州長  我們剛剛聽說
Governor, we just got word
副總統克萊爾·安德伍德
that Vice President Claire Underwood
已宣誓就任代總統
was sworn in as acting president.
您知道嗎
Were you aware?
我當然知道
Of course.
您有什么評論嗎
Do you have any comment?
上帝保佑美國
God bless America.
如果眾議院周一的投票選了您
If Monday's House vote goes your way,
-您成功當選的話  -我會贏的  相信我
- and you win the presidency... - Oh, I'll win, believe me.
您覺得這第三次投票能讓您當選
You think this vote will be the charm?
國會和全國人民心情是一樣的
See, Congress is no different than the rest of the country.
人民厭倦了這種政壇亂局和紛爭
People are sick and tired of all this confusion and chaos.
公眾非常不滿
The public is not happy.
如果您當選總統
If you become president,
克萊爾·安德伍德還會繼續擔任副總統嗎
would Claire Underwood remain as vice president?
如果她為國家大局著想的話  就不會
Not if she wants what's best for the country.
可是第十二修正案有明文規定  你有的選嗎
But given the Twelfth Amendment, would you have a choice?
大家就問到這里吧
Uh, no further questions, everybody.
州長還要和國會議員們會面
The governor's here to talk to members of Congress.
非常感謝各位  謝謝
Thank you so much. Thank you.
謝謝  謝謝大家
Thank you. Thanks, everybody.
-威爾  -我沒事
- Will? - I'm fine.
拉斯姆森也改立場了
And Rasmussen changed his vote.
他一直想找機會報復我
Well, he's been waiting a long time to pay me back.
在羅德島搞出個僵局好讓他博得關注
Creating a deadlock in Rhode Island just gives him the spotlight.
-可以說服他  -會議定在今天下午
- He can be convinced. - Meeting's set for this afternoon.
可如果說服不了他  我們就失去羅德島了
Yes, but if we can't, we lose Rhode Island.
他似乎是一個人  但也可能有別人支持他
He seems to be acting alone, but that could change.
這個周末我們會取得進展的
We will make gains this weekend.
在周一投票前穩住局面
Shore things up by Monday's vote.
總統先生
Mr. President,
我們可能需要考慮另一種選項
it's possible we may need to consider the other option.
改期重新大選
A rescheduled election.
不  我會讓拉斯姆森乖乖的
No, no, I'll get Rasmussen back in line,
順便再多拉幾票過來
and turn some others along the way.
我們已經為你和總統女士安排了
We've arranged sit-downs for you and Madam President
和各小州議員的會面
with all of the small states.
莉安和我可以去雷伯恩  朗沃斯和加農
LeAnn and I can go door-to-door in Rayburn,
三棟眾議院辦公樓逐門拜訪
Longworth and Cannon.
除了白宮  我最喜歡這三棟樓了
Three of my favorite buildings after this one.
什么事
What is it?
南極洲麥克默多研究站
The McMurdo Research Facility in Antarctica.
所有實時通訊渠道都中斷下線了
All live feed communications have ceased or been disconnected.
不過我們收到了一名駐站的
However, we have been receiving texts and e-mails
美國科考人員的短信和電郵
from an American scientist stationed there,
說有身份不明的
claiming that an unidentified
武裝人員實施了登陸占領
occupying military force has landed.
你認為這些士兵是俄軍嗎
You think the soldiers are Russian?
他這么認為
He thinks so.
他們乘坐的是無標記的科考船
They arrived via unmarked research vessels.
我們聯系了莫斯科
We reached out to Moscow,
但他們否認與此事有任何官方聯系
but they're denying any official involvement.
想不到啊
Surprise, surprise.
這就是悍然入侵
It's a brazen act of aggression.
他這是心存僥幸
Well, it's a crime of opportunity.
佩特羅夫認為美國政府現在無暇他顧
Petrov thinks the US government has their eye off the ball.
他想錯了
Well, it doesn't.
凱茜  我們收到的最近一次通訊是什么
Cathy, what's the most recent communication we've received?
我是說  由不明力量發起的
What I'm saying is this aggression in Antarctica,
對南極洲的入侵
by powers unknown,
正是總統之位一事
is a direct result of the uncertainty
遲遲不得以解決造成的直接惡果
that our presidential situation has wrought.
沃茨眾議員  國會黑人黨團什么時候
Congressman Watts, since when is Antarctica a concern
開始這么關心南極洲的事了
for the Congressional Black Caucus?
我希望你不是在暗示
I hope you're not implying that the caucus
黑人黨團無權就國際事務發表意見
shouldn't have a voice in international affairs.
我希望你不是這個意思  謝謝你  蘭迪
I hope that's not what I'm hearing. Thank you, Randy.
我將于明天
I've called a meeting tomorrow,
召集國會黑人黨團開會  在周一總統投票前
for the Congressional Black Caucus, to discuss our positions,
討論本黨團在國內外各項議題上的立場
both foreign and domestic, before Monday's presidential vote.
您是在考慮轉而支持康威嗎
Are you considering shifting your support to Conway?
我現在只能說
Well, all I can say at this time,
最重要的是團結
that the most important thing is unity...
以及民眾對民主制度的信心
and the public's faith in the institution of democracy.
就這樣
That's all for now.
你違反了《南極條約體系》
You are in violation of the Antarctic Treaty System.
那是蘇聯1959年簽訂的條約
A treaty the USSR signed in 1959.
我們已經是個新國家了
We're a new country.
所以你承認了那是你的軍隊
So you're admitting they are your troops.
我只是說我需要
I'm simply stating I need to
解釋一下由蘇聯簽訂的協議
interpret agreements signed by the Soviet Union.
那么
In which case,
你就是否定了幾十年來的裁軍進程
you'd be throwing out decades of disarmament progress.
冷戰已經結束了  代總統女士
The Cold War is over, Mrs. Acting President.
那我們也許需要重新修訂條約
Well, then maybe we need to revisit the treaty.
我對那不感興趣
I'm not interested in revisiting a treaty.
我只關心繼續執政
I'm interested in staying in power.
克萊爾
And, Claire...
如果我能這樣稱呼你的話
if I could be so familiar.
在我的國家
In my country...
一旦你上了臺  就不會放權
once you're in office, you don't let go.
-維克多  -總統先生
- Viktor. - Mr. President.
你們美國人現在的總統可真不少
You Americans certainly have a lot of presidents these days.
是啊  你可能覺得我們無暇他顧
Yes, you may think that we're distracted,
別騙自己了
but don't fool yourself.
無暇他顧  不不不
Distracted? No. No, no.
分裂才對
Divided, yes.
美國的民主制度可比你
American democracy is stronger than your
利用這種小麻煩的可悲企圖強大
sad attempt to take advantage of a bump in the road.
弗蘭西斯  我的關注范圍
Oh, Francis, my eyes are on a landscape
可遠大于你們任何人的前途
that is so much bigger than any one of your roads.
拉斯姆森議員
Well, Congressman Rasmussen,
我們只是驚訝你會
we're just surprised to see you come out
站錯邊  就這樣
on the wrong end of this, is all.
我知道那么多年前
I mean, I suppose it must've been hard
丟掉了眾議院多數黨領袖的位子
losing the House majority leadership
一定很不好受
all those years ago,
但心懷怨憤
but there is a difference
和背叛之間還是有區別的
between being bitter and being treasonous.
如果你是想要新的委員會席位
If it's new committee assignments you'd like,
我們完全可以安排
we can certainly arrange that.
已經結束了
It's over.
市場一落千丈
Markets are in free fall.
消費者信心到了歷史最低點
Consumer confidence is at an all-time low.
這是什么  裝飾品  小玩意
What is this? A doodad? A doohickey?
還是什么沒用的獎品
A... pointless award?
我有說過我討厭沒用的東西嗎
Did I mention I hate useless things?
這個國家已經在崩潰了
This nation is coming apart at the seams.
是因為你  因為你對這個國家做的事
Because of you, because of what you've done to this country.
看吧
There it is.
正義人士總喜歡感慨他們自己中層管理者的角色
How the righteous love to bemoan their role in middle management,
而譴責那些真能影響世界的人
and condemn those who actually might have an effect on the world.
-考慮考慮黨派利益  議員  -我考慮了
- Think of the party, Congressman. - I am.
你覺得你來這兒能怎么樣  弗蘭西斯
What did you think would happen when you came in here, Francis?
你能威脅我
That you could threaten me,
告訴我不合作的話  全國委員會下一輪選舉
tell me the DNC'll throw money at my primary opponent next cycle
就把錢投給我的勁敵
if I don't play ball?
還是說你打算奉承我
Or were you gonna flatter me?
一會兒說我是"黨內長老"
"Elder of the party" this,
一會兒說我是"資深成員領頭羊"
"bellwether senior member" that.
我真有點高興
You know, I'm somewhat delighted
你到了這把年紀還能發展出點個性
that you developed a personality at this late date.
但我希望你再想想
But I would ask you to rethink this.
在你職業生涯的晚期鬧這樣的事情
To come out this way on this thing in the twilight of your career
只會給你的維基百科添一筆污點
will do nothing but sully your Wikipedia page.
你根本不明白  是吧
You have no idea, do you?
你在這里沒有分量了
No one hears you walking the halls of this building...
現在沒有了
not anymore.
-你在幫誰做事  -什么
- Who are you working for? - Excuse me?
我跟你這個軟骨頭共事了二十年
I served next to your jellied spine for two decades.
你從沒表現出過一點勇氣
You've never shown an ounce of courage.
你沒有復仇的本事
You don't have what it takes for revenge.
所以肯定有人給了你不少好處
So someone must have offered you something rather sweet.
好好重新考慮兩小時吧
Take all of the two hours you need to reconsider.
還有一份需要您簽字
One more thing for your signature.
-放在這里就可以了  -好的
- You can leave this with me. - Of course.
-哈維女士在等您  -請讓她進來
- And Miss Harvey's waiting. - Oh, please send her in.
我正要回雷伯恩大樓
I'm on my way back to Rayburn.
請關上門
You close the door, please?
重新投票我們獲勝的可能性有多大
What are our chances with a revote?
或者說  總統獲勝的可能性有多大
Or, rather, what are the president's chances?
我想知道
I want to know.
就全部50個州而言  情況不太好
If it was in all 50 states, not good.
他的反對率還是很高  而你依然低
His unfavorables are still high. Yours are still not.
但他有近30年的經驗  所以也不好說
But it's hard to argue with close to 30 years' experience.
也許總統是對的
Maybe the president is right.
或許他確實在眾議院那里把握更大
Maybe he does have a better chance in the House.
別繞彎子  莉安  告訴我你怎么想的
Don't defer, LeAnn. Tell me what you think.
田納西和俄亥俄的重投是他的最佳機會
The revote in Tennessee and Ohio is his best shot.
這對弗蘭克來說是最佳
While it's what's best for Frank,
可未必對你來說最佳
it may not be what's best for you.
謝謝你
Thank you.
你似乎是個通情達理的人
You seem like a reasonable man.
我懂得傾聽  你是指這個嗎
I know how to listen, if that's what you mean.
如果總統重獲職位
If the president regains his office--
一開口就是如果怎么行  艾力克斯
"If" doesn't make for a winning opener, Alex.
我來這里是因為我覺得他能贏
I'm here because I think he can win.
我和他之間經常會有分歧
We often don't see eye to eye, he and I.
但我們還是可以共事的
And yet, there are ways we can work together.
好吧  委員會那里可能是我錯了
Okay, maybe I made a mistake with the committee.
我有時候會有些自以為是
I can be self-righteous.
我是想清理黨派  我們的黨派
I'm trying to clean up the party. Our party.
結果我說錯話了
And I end up speaking out of turn.
少來"不怪你是我的錯"這一套了
It's enough with the, "It's me, not you."
你到底能做什么  艾力克斯
What can you deliver, Alex?
我可以不礙事
I can get out of the way.
這話太含糊  而且不夠
Well, that sounds vague and inadequate.
我想知道泰瑞·烏麥克和黑人黨團是怎么回事
I want to know what's up with Terry Womack and the Black Caucus.
總統和烏麥克議員
The president and Congressman Womack,
他們關系很好
they have a good relationship.
當然了  但我可不想看到泰瑞讓你們失望
I'm sure they do. But I would hate to see Terry let you down.
如果失去了烏麥克和黑人黨團  我們周一就完了
If we lose Womack and the Black Caucus, we're done on Monday.
有幾個新人我可以搭上關系
There are a few freshmen I could reach out to.
他們或許能讓黑人黨團同心
They might help keep the CBC together.
你想當少數黨黨鞭
You wanna be minority whip.
如果我夠格
Only if I deserve to be.
我準備回去了
I'm trying to get back.
劉易斯議員又遲到了二十分鐘
Congressman Lewis is 20 minutes late as usual.
能讓他進金融服務委員會嗎
Is there a spot for him on financial services?
道格  待著別動
Doug, stay where you are.
你不是說你讓中情局別插手了嗎
I thought you said you were telling the CIA to stand down.
是啊
I did.
你保證過麥卡倫會老實的
So, contrary to your assurances that Macallan would behave,
現在卻出現消息泄露
we're now dealing with a leak.
-他不想惹麻煩  -你怎么知道他想要什么
- He doesn't want trouble. - How do you know what he wants?
你去找到他  帶過來
You find him and you get him here.
只要他知道我們讓步了
As soon as he knows we've backed off,
他就會消失的  我保證
he will disappear. I promise.
不  你的保證對我毫無意義
No, that word means nothing to me.
你寫好聲明了嗎
You have a statement?
還會不會有其他重大的
You anticipate any other big WikiLeaks info dumps
維基解密事件
coming down the pike?
-你會知道的  -等我需要知道的時候
- You'll know-- - When I need to know.
我知道
I know.
也就是上了CNN的時候吧
Which is apparently whenever it hits CNN.
聯調局之前高度戒備  他們調查每個威脅
FBI was on high alert. They investigated every threat.
冷靜
Calm down.
我很冷靜  道格  民眾不冷靜
I am calm, Doug. The public's not calm.
每次失足都被強調  放大
Every misstep is highlighted and heightened.
他們想知道選舉到底怎么回事
They wanna know what happened with their election.
我們正在解決
We're fixing it.
他們怕的就是這個
That's what they're afraid of.
雙關"選舉操縱"
聲明是關于聯調局的  大家都信任聯調局
The statement's about the FBI. Everybody trusts the FBI.
麗薩·威廉姆斯是誰
Hey, who's Lisa Williams?
我不知道  怎么了
I don't know. Why?
《先驅報》有人打電話來
Somebody from the Herald called.
問你認不認識她
They were just wondering if you knew her.
不認識
I don't.
我需要五分鐘審閱
I need five minutes with this.
-給你關門嗎  -關
- Open or closed? - Closed.
我那份聲明怎么樣
Am I good with that statement?
我做好標記了  在我桌子上
I marked it up. It's on my desk.
把選舉交回給各州
Throwing the election back to the states,
讓我們的把握變小了
it gives us less certainty.
我覺得周一之前我們沒法辦妥
I don't think we can get it done by Monday.
我們都已經忙了幾周了  弗蘭西斯
We've been working at it for weeks, Francis.
克萊爾  別因為當職而變得小心翼翼
Claire, don't let the office make you careful.
國會從來沒讓我失望過
The halls of Congress have never failed me.
是  但那些職業政客
Yes, but the career politicians,
他們從沒這么步調一致過
they are more entrenched than ever.
現在有了新眾議院  里面的人你不認識
There's a new House, with members you don't know.
我們得把重點
We need to move the playing field
放回到人民的期望上
back to the imaginations of the people.
你這么相信田納西和俄亥俄的選民嗎
You have that much faith in the voters in Tennessee and Ohio?
他們會選你的  我確定
They're going to choose you. I just know it.
好吧
All right.
安排會議  我會聽他們說的  你贏了
Set up a meeting. I'll hear them all out. You win.
是我們  是我們贏了
Both of us. Both of us.
晚上好
Good evening.
艾瑞克
Eric.
就像是在外面吧
Feel like you're outside?
你不是應該限制在三十分鐘之內嗎
Aren't you supposed to limit it to 30 minutes?
-天啊  可別  -把健身調整好就不必
- Oh, God, Jesus, no. - Not if you calibrate the workout.
我沒事
Oh, I'm feeling fine.
你要聽從你的身體
It's all about listening to your body.
它會告訴你什么時候該休息
It'll tell you when it's time to rest.
你有時也該聽醫生的  弗蘭西斯
You should listen to the doctors some of the time, Francis.
我確定安德伍德夫婦很擔心
I know the Underwoods were worried.
因為他們愿意做交易
Because they were ready to deal.
跟我做交易
To deal with me.
-你能肯定嗎  -非常肯定
- You're sure it's for real? - Sure as I can be.
好  再聯系
Okay, we'll be in touch.
好
Okay.
給他打回去
So call him back.
成功讓幾個民主黨人改主意了
Making progress on a couple of Dems.
阿爾斯波議員也要回心轉意了
Think Congressman Alspaugh is about to turn.
我們周日見他
We'll see him on Sunday.
為什么要等
Why wait?
我們明天得和國會黑人黨團見面
We need to meet with the Congressional Black Caucus. Tomorrow.
他們是安德伍德的
They're in Underwood's pocket.
是啊  能讓我們說句話嗎  各位
Yeah. Can you give us a second, everybody?
好的
Uh, sure.
走吧
Come on.
謝謝
Thank you.
我剛得到內部消息
I just got word from somebody inside.
烏麥克在失去對黨團的控制
Womack is losing control of the caucus.
要是你能拿下他們  周一就贏了
If you win them, you win Monday.
我們應該試試
We should try.
好吧  我們試試吧
All right, fine. Let's do it.
-我去安排  -今晚結束了嗎
- I'll set it up. - Are we done here tonight?
你還得打幾個電話
You still have a few calls.
馬克  我在想我們是不是能
Mark, I was thinking, maybe we could, um...
取消明晚在費城的活動
cancel tomorrow night in Philadelphia.
一趟出行和活動都不能取消  不應該取消
We can't cancel any trip, or any event. We shouldn't.
讓我們稍稍歇歇會大有好處的
A second to catch our breath would be really helpful, I think.
就得這樣  漢娜  需要的話你就休息一下吧
This is what it is, Hannah. If you need to take a break, you can.
親愛的  我們一整周都沒睡了
Darling, we haven't slept all week.
你累壞了
You're exhausted.
-我  只是說說  -下一個打給誰
- I... Just an idea. - What's my next call?
但你不快樂
But you're not enjoying yourself.
因為他不肯聽我的
Because he won't listen to me.
眾議院他贏不了
He can't win in the House.
我說的不是他  我說的是你
I'm not talking about him. I'm talking about you.
我快不快樂又有什么區別呢
What difference does it make whether I'm enjoying myself or not?
這不才是最重要的嗎
Isn't that what this is all about?
你就不能...先體驗它一下嗎
Can't you just... live in it for a second?
你現在掌權了
You are in charge.
-對  但是  -過來
- Yes, but-- - Come here.
過來
Come.
等你明早醒來
You could wake up tomorrow...
你可以
and...
比如  喂孩子們吃飯
I don't know, feed the children...
挑起戰爭
start a war...
你知道嗎  我很抱歉
You know what? I'm sorry.
我不應該把我想的都說出來
I shouldn't think out loud, that's all.
不  你說得對
No, you're right.
我們別談這房間外發生的事了
Let's not talk about anything that happens outside of this room.
制裁的目標是俄羅斯的寡頭階層
The sanctions are meant to target the oligarch class in Russia.
我和佩特羅夫總統談判之前
And the more members we have on board
我們能爭取到越多成員的支持
before I sit down with President Petrov,
這問題就能越快得到解決
the quicker this will resolve itself.
已經在做了  我們準備出售一些戰略儲備
We are. We are prepared to release some of our strategic reserves
以平穩油價
to keep prices down.
聯系卡斯皮大使  再給我爭取15分鐘
Contact Ambassador Caspi and buy me 15 more minutes.
別把這當成是和安德伍德夫婦的交易
Uh, please don't think of this as a deal with the Underwoods.
說實在的  他們可能周一就走了
To be frank, they could be gone by Monday.
但當然了  我不希望這樣
That's not what I wish, of course.
但要知道  在這件事上
But know that you are
你更多是跟我合作  而不是跟他們
working more with me on this than with them.
沃茨議員
Congressman Watts.
州長  真高興你今天來見我們
Governor, we're so happy you could join us today.
我也很高興  黑人群體應該得到更好的政策
As am I. The black community deserves so much better
而不是弗蘭克·安德伍德失敗的政策
than Frank Underwood's failed policies.
這我們都同意
That we can agree on.
我期待你的政綱
I look forward to hearing about your platform.
-我們開始嗎  -不  抱歉
- Shall we? - Oh, no, I'm sorry.
我們還得再處理一些閉門的
We have just a bit more private caucus business
黨團議程
to attend to first.
你說什么
Excuse me?
這是國會黑人黨團的會議
This is a meeting of the Congressional Black Caucus.
我知道  所以我們才來
Well, I understand. That's... why we're here.
跟我說的是九點  現在已經過了一個小時了
I was told 9:00, and it's already been an hour.
應該叫你十點來的
You should have been told 10:00.
你會有機會跟我們談的
And you will get your opportunity to address us.
很感謝你的耐心等待
I appreciate your patience.
我不會低聲下氣的
I'm not gonna beg.
對  你要微笑
No, you're gonna smile.
在田納西被捕的穆罕默德·卡拉比
The Muhammed Kalabi they arrested in Tennessee
和哈里發國并無關聯
is not the Kalabi connected to ICO.
你能證明這不是單純的搞錯了嗎
Can you prove it wasn't just a bureaucratic mix-up?
目前還沒有證據
Uh, not yet.
還有什么
What else?
最后一宗壓制投票訴訟
Uh, final voter suppression lawsuit
被踢回了下級法院
was kicked back to the lower court,
高院的僵持助長了混亂局面
SCOTUS deadlock is feeding the chaos.
你看報嗎  肖恩
Do you read the paper, Sean?
比利三天前就署名發表了關于這個的報道
Billy got a byline on that three days ago.
宣戰怎么樣
Declaration of war?
安德伍德之前還決心滿滿
Underwood was so evangelical,
但他已經幾周沒提起這個了
but hasn't mentioned it in weeks.
行了  夠了  夠了
All right, that's enough. That's enough.
麗薩·威廉姆斯
Lisa Williams.
麗莎·威廉姆斯怎么了
What about Lisa Williams?
我看見你和她交談了
I saw you talking.
我認為她這條線可能值得追查
I thought she might be a lead worth pursuing.
并不
She's not.
她只是在利用在報上看到的東西
She's using what she read in the paper
博取關注或是發點小財
to get attention or a little cash.
我調查了一下
I did some digging.
她和瑞秋·波斯納
She and Rachel Posner
都去過一個叫團契的教堂
both went to a church called the Fellowship.
-瑞秋失蹤了  -打住
- Rachel disappeared-- - Stop.
別再扯這些關于死去姑娘的陰謀論了
No more conspiracy theories about dead girls.
但人們喜歡看死去姑娘的故事
But people love stories about dead girls.
下一場眾議院投票就在后天了
The next House vote is the day after tomorrow.
國民坐立不安  義憤填膺
The natives are restless, outraged,
而且說實話  害怕了
just plain scared, actually.
他們希望美國不會一夜天翻地覆
They want to wake up in the America that they fell asleep in.
卡拉比那條線再挖挖
Dig deeper on the Kalabi lead.
看看能不能和安德伍德聯系到一起去
See if you can connect Underwood to it.
這是詹姆斯·S·布雷迪媒體接待室
So, this is the James S. Brady press briefing room.
我們腳下其實是個游泳池
And under our feet is actually a swimming pool.
是由畸形兒基金會為
It was built by the March of Dimes
富蘭克林·羅斯福總統建造的
for President Franklin Roosevelt,
他患了小兒麻痹癥
who had polio.
泳池是他唯一的健身場所
And this pool was really the only way for him to exercise.
羅斯福總統大部分時間
It was, an open secret
都是在輪椅上度過  這已是個公開的秘密了
that the president used a wheelchair most of the time.
因此白宮
Which is why the White House
是首批有殘疾人專用通道的政府建筑之一
was one of the first wheelchair-accessible government buildings.
-但大家都裝作他能走路嗎  -是的
- But everyone pretended he could walk? - Yes.
-這很有風度  -是的
- That's a bit of grace. - Yeah.
大家都心照不宣
A thing not spoken?
是的  這座大樓因為他的殘疾而進行了改建
Yeah, this building literally changed because of his disability.
但人們都很尊敬他
But people just respected him,
尊敬他的...
respected his, uh--
嗯
Right.
總統辦公室曾承載了很重的分量
That office used to carry so much weight,
和很多尊敬
so much, respect.
你覺得現在已經不是如此了嗎
You don't think it does anymore?
不不  我沒那個意思
No, oh, no, no! I'm not saying that.
我是在故意為難你  我明白你的意思
I was giving you a hard time. I know what you meant.
抱歉  我無意打擾你們參觀的
Anyway, sorry, didn't mean to hijack the tour.
繼續...
Moving on...
先生們  我們可以見你們了
Gentlemen, we're ready for you now.
我今天可以在這兒
I could come here today
談論大麻和可卡因的
and talk about federal sentencing disparities
聯邦量刑差異
between crack and cocaine,
這其中顯然存在種族因素
which obviously are racially motivated.
打斷一下  你是斷定濫用大麻的問題
I'm sorry, but are you asserting that the crack epidemic
只在黑人群體中存在嗎
is exclusive to the black community?
不  完全不是
No, not at all.
但我覺得可以說  量刑差異
But I think it's fair to say that sentencing discrepancies
對少數群體的影響尤為嚴重
have disproportionately affected minority populations.
我們不只關注一個問題
We're not one-issue voters.
當然不是  這正是我的意思
Of course not. That's what I'm getting at.
今天會議的主旨就是擴展我們的綱領
The whole point of today's meeting is to broaden our platform.
共和黨總是拿犯罪說事  州長
Republicans are always dwelling on crime, Governor.
我就是來溝通的
Well, I'm here to have a dialogue.
我們希望你能拿出一個方案來
We expected you to come in here with a plan.
我確實準備了一套方案
And I do have a plan.
專注于個別繁瑣的立法不叫方案
Concentrating on a few pieces of onerous legislation is not a plan.
讓我們把話說清楚...
Let's be clear...
這樣的說辭我們聽過
That kind of talk we've heard before.
-我是共和黨人  -又來了
- I'm a Republican. - Here we go.
你們沒有好好聽我說
You're not listening.
我想幫助你們自力更生
Look, I want to help you help yourselves.
不可理喻
Unbelievable.
這就是我的綱領
That's my platform.
是嗎  我聽夠了
Well... I've heard enough.
還有誰有問題想問州長
So, does anyone else have any questions for the governor?
我倒是有個問題
Well, I have a question.
弗蘭西斯·安德伍德到底給了你們什么好處
What has Francis Underwood ever done for you?
今天早上的這出戲
This little charade this morning...
-演得好  真精彩  -威爾
- Well done. Quite an act. - Will.
-州長  -我說真的
- Governor. - No, but really.
你們也許和我有分歧
See, you may have differences with me...
你們也許真心不贊同我的觀點
You may have genuine differences with me.
但最關鍵的就是這一點  "真心"
But see, that's the operative word, "genuine."
能否麻煩你們哪位給我解釋一下
Can someone here please explain to me
你們為什么還對
why you all are still so loyal
弗蘭西斯·安德伍德和民主黨這么忠誠
to Francis Underwood and the Democrats?
總有一天
One of these days
在座的各位會意識到
the members of this room will realize
目前的現狀  你們要負多大的責任
how much you actually prop up the status quo.
你們撈著什么好處了嗎
And how's that working for ya?
威爾  我們先感謝各位先生女士見我們吧
Will, why don't we thank the gentlemen and women for their time?
你們犯了個錯誤
You've made a mistake.
選舉人到華盛頓進行最后投票前6天
我們提議在兩個未能在安全港日之前
What we're proposing is a new election in the two states
選出有效選舉人的州
that weren't able to provide valid electors
重新舉行大選
by the safe harbor date.
還能這么做
Can we even do this?
安靜  大家安靜
Hold on. Hold on, everyone!
我想知道
I'd like to know,
司法部長是什么立場
where does the attorney general stand on this?
正在研究  不過也同意了
Looking into it, but on board.
鮑勃  這種事根本沒有先例
Bob, there's no precedent here.
沒有現成的規則
There's no playbook.
我們只能在憲法里尋找啟示
We can look to the Constitution for inspiration,
但它不是操作指南
but not for instruction.
周四的投票表明民主黨人漸漸想明白了
Thursday's vote showed Democrats are coming to their senses.
我們輸了一場投票  喬丹
We lost one vote, Jordan.
這事完全可能搞成拉鋸戰
We can go back and forth like this forever.
作為在場少數的幾個共和黨  我必須要說
As one of the few Republicans in the room, it needs to be said.
我們國家的穩定
The stability of our country
要比總統職位重要得多
is more important than the presidency.
除非民眾認為他們的總統
Not if people believe the president
是秘密會議指定的
is being chosen behind closed doors.
這是憲法里寫明的程序
A process that is laid out in the Constitution.
而這個程序完全可能讓我們
The same process that can keep us gridlocked
再僵持兩年
for the next two years.
決定權應該且必須歸于眾議院
The House should and will decide.
特拉華州只有一個眾議員
Delaware has one congressman.
如果兩年后你的對手告訴選民  是你
How will that play in Austin when your opponent in two years
讓特拉華這樣的小州和德州有相同的影響力
tells voters that you allowed a state like Delaware
你在奧斯丁還要怎么待
to have the same influence as Texas?
你們許多在任議員都將可能敗選
A lot of you incumbents will be in danger of losing your seats.
就是這樣
And there it is.
看啊  看看他們
Look. Look at them.
這就是忌憚失敗的表情
That is the look of contemplating loss.
失敗
Loss...
是這里所有人唯一聽從的選民
the only constituent that anyone in this room really listens to.
我個人想聽一下
I, for one, would like to hear
總統對此的看法
how the president feels about all this.
-我已經...  -我想我們可以
- Well, I've made my... - I think we could...
我是問總統先生  您剛才一直沒說什么
No, Mr. President. You haven't spoken much here.
我們相信一人一票
We believe in one person, one vote.
如果不能做到這點  我們國家還算什么
If we take that away, then what is this country?
對不對  總統先生
Isn't that right, Mr. President?
完全正確  總統女士
Absolutely, Madam President.
等等  等下  我往下挪挪
Wait, hold it. Let me just move down a bit.
我老是要從講臺上滑下來
I keep slipping off the podium.
-你接著我  -好些了嗎
- You got me. - That better?
嗯  好爽
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
話說林肯室
So the Lincoln...
那真是他的辦公室嗎
That was actually his office?
能不說工作嗎
Can we... can we not?
-你能  把我往上托一托嗎  -好
- Can you... can you move me up a bit? - Yeah.
好了
Okay.
-還順利嗎  -再看吧
- How'd it go? - We'll see.
我需要你再過一遍南極洲事件的聲明稿
I need you to look over the Antarctica statement again.
都聽你的
Whatever you need.
陪我走走吧
Walk with me?
我有點擔心弗蘭西斯
I'm worried about Francis.
-為什么  -我可能需要你幫我一把
- Why? - I might need you to save me.
-這樣是不行的  -為什么
- This is not going to work. - Why?
如果他沒贏  那我還是輸
If he loses, I still lose.
他不能站在圈外看著我們忙活
He cannot be on the outside looking in.
他會贏的
He'll win.
你真的這么想
You actually believe that?
當然  為什么不呢
Sure... why not?
這本就是賭一把
It was a wager.
有潛在收益  所以有必要賭
The potential gains made it necessary.
完全是浪費我的時間
It was a complete waste of my time.
如果你還不開始扭轉局勢
If you don't start turning things around,
你他媽就得滾蛋  明白嗎
you're going to be out on your fucking ass. You understand?
明白
I do.
我該跟你說明白一件事  州長
I should explain something to you, Governor.
如果你再那樣跟我說話
If you ever talk to me like that again...
我會確保你這輩子再贏不了一場選舉
I'll make sure you never win another election in your life.
-你在威脅我嗎  -不  我只是把話說開
- Are you threatening me? - No, I'm enlightening you.
康威州長  你好  先生
Governor Conway. Hello, sir.
情況如何  我來看看
How you doin'? Take a peek,
-你不介意吧  機長  -州長
- if you don't mind, Captain? - Governor.
我過去也開過飛機
I used to fly, too, you know.
引擎的最大推力是多少
What kinda max thrust you get on these engines?
-約六千四百磅  -六千四百磅
- About 6,400 pounds. - 6,400 pounds.
我過去開的飛機更大  推力更強
I used to fly something a lot bigger, a lot more power,
但飛機上的武器很重
but it was so weighed down with all the weaponry,
像在駕駛坦克
it was like flying a tank.
不如你讓我開會兒
Why don't you let me in for a second,
讓我控制操縱桿
just flip me the controls?
抱歉  先生  不行
I'm sorry, sir. I can't.
別這樣  我...
Come on, I...
我只是想感受一下操縱桿的力道
I just want to feel the weight on the stick for a second.
我也想  但你不在飛行計劃中
I wish I could, but, uh, you're not on the flight plan.
你知道我經驗豐富吧
You know I've been in situations,
我遭遇過攻擊
where, like, I've been shot at.
你明白吧
You realize that, right?
你覺得我駕馭不了十千米高空中的雙引擎
You don't think I can handle a twin engine at 35,000 feet,
飛機還是平穩地飛越農田
straight and level over some farm country?
拜托  先生
I mean, come on, sir.
先生
Sir.
您還是回主艙吧
You should probably go back to the main cabin.
你知道我會成為總統吧
You know I'm gonna be the president, right?
-希望如此  先生  -你希望如此
- I hope so, sir. - You hope so?
我只是說我支持你  先生
I just mean I'm pulling for you, sir.
我一定會成為總統
I'm gonna be the president,
你也一定要把那該死的操縱桿給我
and you're going to flip me those motherfucking controls.
威爾  過來
Will, come on.
-干嗎  你想怎樣  -我只是
- What? What do you want? - I just
得跟你談一會兒  行嗎
I need to talk to you for a minute, please.
我只是在跟飛行員聊天
I was just talking to the pilots.
行  你得冷靜下來  行嗎
Okay, I need you to calm down, okay?
呼吸
Breathe.
威爾  不如你坐下
Will, why don't you sit down?
不如你他媽閉嘴
Why don't you shut the fuck up?
我要炒了你
I'll fire you.
把你留在跑道上
I'll leave you on the goddamn tarmac.
好吧
Okay.
你他媽想怎樣
What the fuck are you gonna do?
坐下來  別耍孩子氣
Sit down and try and act like an adult...
至少要有點下任美國總統的樣子
or at least like the next President of the United States.
坐下
Sit.
他們是誰
Who are they?
或許是印尼的秘密警察
Maybe Indonesian secret police?
不付錢會怎樣
What if we don't pay?
還有其他買家嗎
Are there other buyers?
不清楚
I don't know.
我會處理好的
I'll take care of it.
-怎么做  -別問我
- How? - Don't ask how.
我會找回麥卡倫
I'll get Macallan back.
顯然這事得保密
Obviously, this stays between us.
說"謝謝  道格"
Say, "Thank you, Doug."
謝謝  道格
Thank you, Doug.
我們在公交車上認識的
We met on a bus.
她當時在聽歌
She was listening to music.
我問她要不要去我以前常去的一間教堂
And I asked her to go to this church I used to go to.
-那是在哪  -馬里蘭
- Where was that? - Maryland.
冬離團契
The Winter's Run Fellowship.
巴爾的摩往北一小時路程
About an hour north of Baltimore.
然后呢
So, then what?
我們就是...
I don't know. We just...
成了朋友  然后就超越了朋友
became friends. And then it became more than that.
開始每晚在一起
Started spending every night together.
后來  她告訴我有個男人
At some point, she told me about this guy
常常過去查看她的情況
who used to come around to check on her.
-那男人長什么樣  -我沒見過他
- What'd he look like? - I never saw him.
只是有時  她說他要來
Just sometimes she said he was coming,
就沒法跟我在一起
so she couldn't hang out.
她并不怎么跟我講他的事
She wouldn't really tell me anything about him.
你沒事吧
Everything okay?
沒事  失陪一下
Yeah, do you mind?
我朋友在那邊  我得去見他
I just need to see my friend up there.
你好嗎
How are you doing?
謝謝
Thanks.
你認為那兒有石油
You think there's oil there.
你想爭取開采權
You're positioning to stake a claim.
南極洲并沒有俄國軍隊
There are no Russian troops in Antarctica.
我們愿對《南極條約》締約國
We're willing to recommend changes
提出修改建議
to the Antarctic Treaty parties.
安德伍德夫婦被趕出白宮后  你會怎么樣
What happens to you when the Underwoods are ejected from office?
到大學去教國際關系
You teach international relations at a university?
還是加入智囊團
Or work for a think tank?
我還沒想那么遠
I haven't thought that far ahead.
你應該有吧
I think you have.
你不覺得全世界遲早會發現
How long do you expect the world to believe
那是你的軍隊嗎
those aren't your soldiers?
你喜歡替安德伍德夫婦工作嗎
Do you like working for the Underwoods?
你有多忠誠
How loyal are you?
關鍵時刻  你會支持他們
When the time comes, will you stand with them...
還是拋棄他們
or not?
我明天離開
I leave tomorrow.
關于制裁的新聞會在周一爆出
News of the sanctions will hit Monday.
你走之前我們見個面
Let's meet before you go.
你是外交專家  專業人士
You're a career diplomat, a professional.
或許因此我信任你
Maybe that's why I trust you.
你會照顧他們
Then you take care of them,
他們感覺好了  就會照顧你
so they feel good and they take care of you.
那你就會感覺好...
So you feel good because...
瑞秋美麗動人
I mean, Rachel was really beautiful.
你站在街對面就能看得出來
You could tell that from across the street.
但我從來沒有隔著街看過她
I never saw her from across the street, though.
仔細想想是不是很奇妙
Isn't that a funny thing to think about?
我覺得  有時候
A lot of people, I think,
很多人隔著街就能認出他們的心上人
they spot the one they love from across the street sometimes.
比如說他們出門辦事
It's like they're running an errand,
碰巧看見他們的心上人
and they happen to spot the one they love
在街對面  辦著別的事
across the street running a different errand.
心里一陣激動
There's this sudden thrill, like...
因為你的愛人
while the person you love
和你居住在同一個世界
is inhabiting the same world as you.
而他們只是很隨意地
And they're just walking around,
出門買個維生素水之類的
buying, I don't know... Vitaminwater,
或許他們這么做時  知道你愛著他們
and maybe they know that you love them while they're doing it,
或許他們因此會對店員友善
and maybe it means they're nice to a cashier.
但是我從來沒有隔著街看過她
I never got to see her from across the street, though.
從來沒有
It just never happened.
別燙傷自己了
I don't want you to burn yourself.
不會燙傷的
No burning, no.
瑞秋愛抽煙
Rachel liked to smoke.
她說打算戒掉
She said she was gonna stop,
但她定了個規則  只有我們一起聽
but she would have a rule that she'd only smoke
我們共同喜愛的樂隊時  她才能抽煙
when we listened to this one band we both loved.
因為那是儀式
Because of the ceremony.
"這該成為一個儀式"  她這么說的
"It should be a ceremony," it's what she said.
即使是口香糖
Well, even if it's gum,
我還是想到外面嚼
I still prefer to step outside to chew it.
像是在點燃一根美味的香煙
Like lighting a delicious cigarette.
我們所懷念的  那種儀式感
The things we miss, the rituals...
我先走了
Excuse me.
-她不喜歡我  -她以后會的
- She doesn't like me. - She will.
感謝你過來和他見面
Thanks for coming out here and meeting with him.
你知道法律上  你無法趕走克萊爾·安德伍德
You know you can't legally remove Claire Underwood,
即便你在眾議院獲勝
even if you win in the House?
我正在想辦法
I'm working on that.
我沒興趣
I'm not interested.
他需要你  我需要你
He needs you. I need you.
國家也需要你
So does the country.
我不是政客
I'm not a politician.
我能下達命令  也能遵從命令
I can give orders, I can follow orders
我知道何時該閉嘴
and I know when the hell to shut up.
你是個穩重的人  國家需要這種人
And you're a steady hand, which, again, the country needs.
-我可不當康威的替死鬼  -你不會的
- I'm not gonna be Conway's patsy. - No, you're not.
他是個難相處的人
He's a difficult man to be around.
已經結束了
It's over. It's over.
憲法程序選擇了克萊爾·安德伍德
The process chose Claire Underwood.
我們會有辦法的
We'll get there.
你會被稱為副總統
You'll be called vice president,
但實際上  你將做到更多
but you will be, de facto, something more.
你去那兒做什么
What were you doing there?
我去問賽斯·格雷森關于麗薩·威廉姆斯的事
I asked Seth Grayson about Lisa Williams.
你為什么會認為可以這么做
Why the hell did you think that was an appropriate thing to do?
我不是叫你別管這條線索了嗎
Didn't I tell you to drop this lead?
這還算線索嗎  因為沒人在查
Is it still a lead? Because nobody's on it.
沒人在查是因為她是癮君子
Nobody's on it because she's a junkie,
而她告訴我的一切
and everything she said to me
盧卡斯·古德溫的宣言里都有
is in the Lucas Goodwin manifesto,
而宣言的每一字每一句  都被網上各大論壇
which has been picked apart by every message board
和陰謀論者掰爛嚼碎了
and conspiracy theorist on the Internet.
一開始  格雷森說對她的名字沒印象
At first, Grayson said her name didn't ring a bell,
然后他突然聯系我
but then he called me out of the blue
問我是不是還在查這個事
and asked me if we were still looking into it.
所以我就查了
So I followed up.
你偷看了我的筆記
You looked through my notes.
滾
You're out.
-什么  -你被開除了  杰弗瑞斯
- What? - You're fired, Jeffries.
這是個故事  我在跟進這個故事
It's a story. I was following it.
我不希望你跟著我干了
I don't want you on my team.
滾出我的辦公室
Get out of my office.
我們知道我們能贏下這兩個州
We know we can win both states.
為什么不接受這個交易
Why would we not take this deal?
不  安德伍德夫婦想重新投票
No. The Underwoods want a revote
是因為他們知道拿不下眾議院  而我們能
because they know they can't win in the House. We can.
我們要做個交易  逼克萊爾·安德伍德辭職
We need to make a deal that forces Claire Underwood to resign.
-她有那么重要嗎  -我能說兩句嗎
- And why does that matter? - If I may?
-議長女士  -就國會而言
- Madam Speaker. - Speaking from the Hill,
作為副總統
as vice president,
她可以利用這個平臺公開抹黑你的所有動作
she'll have a public pulpit to discredit your every move.
美國副總統官邸
我會把克萊爾·安德伍德流放到海軍天文臺I'm going to exile Claire Underwood to the Naval Observatory
讓她整天在東南亞出席國葬儀式
and stack her schedule with state funerals in Southeast Asia.
她別想參與白宮的決策
She'll never see the inside of the West Wing,
更別提干涉總統了
let alone the Oval.
你需要布洛哈特在你身邊支持你
You need Brockhart by your side, supporting you.
我不想再聽布洛哈特的事了
I don't want to hear about Brockhart.
重要的是讓威爾當上總統
What matters is that Will becomes president.
安德伍德在你的政府里會造成巨大破壞的
Underwood in office can cause an enormous amount damage.
反過來如果他們輸了  他們就全完了
Whereas, if they lose, they're losers.
我希望這場選舉是在我
I want this election to be between me
和弗蘭西斯·安德伍德之間
and Francis Underwood.
這你說了不算
Well, it isn't up to you.
麥卡錫議長不會讓這個議案進入投票的
Speaker McCarthy isn't letting this particular bill to the floor,
除非我們附加一項修正案
unless we have an amendment attached
將克萊爾·安德伍德趕走
that removes Claire Underwood.
威爾
Will...
如果你希望白宮里有位愿意合作的總統
Now, if you expect a willing partner in the White House,
那你最好讓議案原樣進入表決
you'd better let that bill get to the floor as is.
如果你坐進總統辦公室  威爾
If you get to the Oval, Will,
那時是你更需要議長  而不是反過來
you're gonna need the Speaker more than she needs you.
我這就給她打回去
So, I'm gonna call her back,
然后你要道歉
and you are going to apologize.
威爾
Will.
威爾  回來
Will, get back here!
威爾
Will!
別逼他了
Enough.
關門
Shut the door.
你看著像死人
You look like death.
我聯系不上綁匪了
I can't get in touch with the kidnappers.
快一天了  什么消息都沒有
It's been radio silence for almost 24 hours.
有傳言說他已經不在綁匪手上了
There's rumors they don't even have him anymore.
這事我不能再瞞著總統了
I can't keep this from the president any longer.
好吧
Okay.
那我會告訴他你幫了好大的忙
And then I'll tell him what a big help you've been.
再過幾小時制裁就要生效了
Sanctions hit in a couple of hours.
你要么和杜蘭特國務卿談
Deal with Secretary Durant
要么對付幾個憤怒的億萬富翁去吧
or with some very unhappy billionaires.
你要讓我在南極洲任意開采石油
You will allow me to exploit whatever oil I find in Antarctica.
我告訴你為什么
And I'll tell you why.
我手上有料
I have something.
或者說有你們想要的人
Or rather, someone you need.
你在說什么
What are you talking about?
你們政府里有人
Someone in your administration
愿花大錢換他平安回國
was willing to pay a great deal of money for his safe return.
你的艾丹·麥卡倫
Your Aidan Macallan.
他在這里  就在克里姆林宮里
He's here. In the Kremlin.
不然你以為是誰泄的密
Who do you think orchestrated that leak?
看來他知道的不少啊
Seems to know quite a lot.
失陪一下  你們國務卿來了
Excuse me one moment. The Secretary of State is here.
-國務卿女士  -先生們
- Madam Secretary. - Gentlemen.
想必你認識艾丹吧
You must know Aidan?
我想我不認識他
I don't believe I do.
很高興認識你
Nice to meet you.
-你是美國人  -是
- You're American? - I am.
開始會談之前  我想讓你知道
Before we begin, I'd just like you to know that
你們的總統和前總統都在線上
the president and the former president are on the line.
凱茜
Cathy...
你愿意的話可以接聽
You can pick up the phone, if you like.
總統先生
Mr. President.
你最好先回華盛頓
It's best you come back to Washington.
有什么發現嗎
Find anything yet?
還沒
Not yet.
再次感謝  巴恩斯先生
Thank you again, Mr. Barnes,
謝謝你讓我看
for letting me take a look.
我不會看太久
I won't be long.
這就是全部嗎
This is everything?
這是他們從佐伊的公寓寄來的一切
This is everything they sent from Zoe's apartment.
我就是
I just, you know...
我不忍扔掉任何東西
I just can't seem to throw anything out.
只是些文件  但是
I mean, it's just papers, but...
不管怎樣  你自便
Anyway, I'll leave you to it.
-好  謝謝  -沒事
- Okay. Thank you. - Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
黑人黨團  不是吧
The Black Caucus? Really?
我喜歡馬克  因為我總是知道他的立場
I like Mark, because I always know where he stands.
通常是對人步步緊逼
It's usually on someone's neck.
你給自己爭取到了什么  一天時間嗎
What did you buy yourselves, another day?
足夠跟大衛·拉斯姆森談了
Enough time to talk to David Rasmussen,
顯然你早就跟他談過
who you clearly spoke to before.
然后又見了喬丹·薩多斯基
And to meet with Jordan Sadowsky
和剩下的共和黨領導人
and the rest of the Republican leadership.
那星期二呢  星期三呢
And what happens Tuesday? Or Wednesday?
我能讓大衛和眾議院
Look, I... I can have David and the House
每次會議都對此進行投票
vote on this every single session.
我們背景不同
Our backgrounds are different,
但內心里我們都是窮小子
but we're both hardscrabble boys at heart.
我們需要最后一個字  最后一擊
We need the last word, last blow,
最后一舉
last move.
我們能讓眾議院通過議案
We can push the bill through the House
在田納西州和俄亥俄州重新選舉總統
for a new election for president in Tennessee and Ohio.
麥卡錫議長不會允許那種事發生
Speaker McCarthy won't let that happen.
但我能說服她
But I could... convince her
如果你辭職
if you were to step down,
我們在田納西州和俄亥俄州
and our full tickets president and vice president
同時進行總統和副總統的選舉
run against each other in Tennessee and Ohio.
那可不行  那可不行
Well, to hell with that. Well, to hell with that.
我們接受交易  我想這是正確的做法
We'll make the deal. I think this is the right thing to do.
明天我會宣布
Tomorrow, I'll announce my intention
在重新投票后我就辭職
to step down after the revote.
我會通知議長讓議案進入投票表決
I'll let the Speaker know to put the bill on the floor.
我們還有一件非常重要的事
We have one more outstanding piece of business,
最高法院提名人
the Supreme Court nominee.
我們需要任命個人來打破四四僵局
We'll need to appoint someone to break the four-four deadlock.
批準國會的新選舉日
Approve Congress' new election date.
我們有幾個人選
We, uh, have several people in mind.
我希望你們任命伊麗莎白·本森
I want you to appoint Elizabeth Benson.
她足夠開放  你可以接受
Well, she's liberal enough for you to swallow,
必要的時候又足夠保守
and conservative enough when it counts.
但我們沒時間開參議院聽證會
Yes, but we don't have time for Senate hearings.
我可以讓參議院休會
I can make a recess happen.
競選活動上見
I'll see you on the campaign trail.
那置我于何地  艾力克斯
Where does that leave me, huh, Alex?
我冒了巨大風險
I went out on a limb here.
如果我們沒拿下眾議院  那怎么辦
If we don't have a vote in the House, then what?
馬克·厄舍是你的朋友  不是我的
Mark Usher is your friend, not mine.
馬克·厄舍不是任何人的朋友
Mark Usher's no one's friend.
弗蘭西斯·安德伍德什么也沒贏  好嗎
Francis Underwood hasn't won a thing, okay?
威爾·康威有可能  很大的可能
And there's a good... More than a good chance that Will Conway
會成為下一任美國總統
will be the next President of the United States.
能讓我單獨待會兒嗎  這幾天太艱難了
Could you give me a moment? It's been a difficult few days.
好點嗎
Better?
嗯
Yes.
我們不能按原計劃讓眾議院周一投票
We couldn't let the House vote proceed on Monday.
為什么
Why not?
因為你會輸的
Because you would've lost.
即使康威當了總統
Even if Conway took the presidency,
有你  我們還是會有立足之地
we would've had a foothold with you.
我們可以破壞他們  就像對沃克夫婦那樣
We could've sabotaged, just like we did with the Walkers.
康威夫婦不是沃克夫婦
The Conways are not the Walkers.
那不是你能決定的
It wasn't your decision to make.
你說什么
Excuse me?
你自己說的  你只是代總統
You said it yourself. You're only acting.
我贊同厄舍
I agreed with Usher
是因為他會不惜一切
because he will sacrifice everything
讓布洛哈特上位
to get Brockhart into office,
而這就讓康威變弱  容易失敗
which makes Conway weak, ready to lose.
我以為你和我看法相同
I thought you saw what I saw.
確實
I did. I do.
我們完全同步  克萊爾
We're perfectly in sync, Claire.
最高法院基本任命流程是  當法院出現空缺  總統提名一個人選
然后參議院舉行公開聽證會  一般持續三到五天
然后參議院進行投票  如果被提名者獲得多數票  就可以宣誓就職
歷史上也出現過休會任命大法官
但休會任命的局限是  在參議院復會后  還是要進行任命投票
在最高法院大法官的任命投票上  民主黨在控制參議院時
取消了原有的阻撓議事  允許51票簡單多數即可過關
這種規則的更改  卻讓共和黨占了便宜
在不久前特朗普提名大法官后  因為目前共和黨控制了參議院
雖然民主黨非常反對  但共和黨仍靠簡單多數投票讓大法官上任了
在美國早期  現代政黨系統還沒有成型的時候
出現過正副總統分屬不同黨派的情況
亞當斯做總統時  副總統杰斐遜跟他不是一個黨派
創立了共和黨的林肯  出于選舉策略的考慮  選了民主黨杰克遜做副總統
根據法律  這種情況是可能出現的
因為一旦選舉結果有爭議  需要國會來投票選舉總統時
總統是由眾議院選舉產生  而副總統是由參議院選舉產生
這就可能出現正副總統不同黨  但歷史上沒有發生過